Mss.B.W564
American Philosophical Society
- VI. Works by Others, 1926-1987 (Volume 90-110, Box 83-128)
  - Nonexistence of baryon number for static black holes, 1972; Bekenstein, Jacob David (Box 85)
  - Time dependent interior Riesner-Nordstrom solution and the charge-mass relation for a black hole, Bekenstein, Jacob David (Box 85)
  - [Unidentified manuscript], 1980; Bekenstein, Jacob David (Box 85)
  - Symmetry breaking induced by charge density and the entropy of interacting fields, 1986; Bekenstein, Jacob David; Guendelman, E. I. (Box 85)
  - Godel for Wheeler, [1975]; Benda, Miroslav (Box 85)
  - Relation of a theory of countable sets to the field equations of physics, [1984]; BenDaniel, David J. (Box 85)
  - Ideology of science, [1972]; Bendix, Reinhard (Box 85)
  - Finite and infinite measurement sequences in quantum mechanics, randomness, and the Everett Wheeler interpretation, [1977]; 2.0 folders; Benioff, Paul A. (Box 85)
  - Note on the Everett interpretation of quantum mechanics, [1977]; Benioff, Paul A. (Box 85)
  - Quantum mechanical Hamiltonian models of discrete processes that erase their own histories: Application to Turing machines, [1977]; Benioff, Paul A. (Box 85)
  - Unitary field theories, [1979]; Bergmann, Peter Gabriel (Box 85)
    Originally enclosed in Series II: Physics Today, 24 January 1979
  - Albert Einstein -- A moral visionary in a distraught world, 1979; Berl, Walter G., (Walter George), b. 1917 (Box 85)
    Page proof. Originally enclosed in Series III: Albert Einstein Material
  - Black holes and quantum geometrodynamics, 1971; Bernstein, Steven (Box 85)
  - Aspects of degeneracy, [1983]; Berry, Michael V. (Box 86)
  - Breaking the paradigms of classical physics from within, 1983; Berry, Michael V. (Box 86)
  - Quantum phase factors accompanying adiabatic changes, 1983; Berry, Michael V. (Box 86)
  - Semiclassical mechanics of regular and irregular motion, 1981; Berry, Michael V. (Box 86)
  - Diabolical points on the spectra of triangles, 1983; Berry, Michael V.; Wilkinson, M. (Box 86)
  - Bifurcation from the Maclaurin to the Jacobi sequence as a second order phase transition, 1975; Bertin, G., (Giuseppe); Radicati, L. A., (Luigi Arialdo), b. 1919 (Box 86)
  - Introduction to general relativity...the quasiuniform field problem, [1980]; Bertoldi, Philip E. (Box 86)
  - Old and new frameworks for experiments on gravity, 1977; Bertotti, B., 1930- (Box 86)
  - Equation of state in the gravitational collapse of stars, 1978; Bethe, Hans A., (Hans Albrecht), 1906-2005; et al (Box 86)
  - An insight into Mach's Principle, 1976; Beven, Terry P. (Box 86)
  - Baryons as quarks in Skyrmion bubble, 1984; Biedenharn, Lawrence C.; Dothan, Y.; Stern, Alan, 1957- (Box 86)
  - Head on collision of identically charged particles in one-half advanced plus one-half retarded electrodynamics, [1986]; Bishop, Robert C. (Box 86)
  - On the dynamics of two charged particles described by action at a distance, n.d.; Bishop, Robert C. (Box 86)
    Originally enclosed in Series III: Half-retarded, Half-advanced Potentials
  - One dimensional two-body problem in action-at-a-distance electrodynamics and corporate degrees of freedom, 1986; Bishop, Robert C. (Box 86)
  - Harmoni og enhed: Niels Bohr en biografi, [1985]; 2.0 folders; Blaedel, Niels (Box 86)
    In Danish
  - Edward Teller: Giant of the golden age of physics, 1986; Blumberg, Stanley A.; Panos, Louis G. (Box 86)
    Drafts of Introduction, Chapters 1 and 2
  - Proposed back action evading read-out for a gravitational wave detector, 1983; Bocko, Mark Frederick, 1956-; et al (Box 87)
  - New relativistic generalization of the Heisenberg commutation relations, 1984; Bohm, Arno, 1936- (Box 87)
  - Quantum mechanics, 1978; Bohm, Arno, 1936- (Box 87)
  - Rigged Hilbert space and decaying states, 1978; Bohm, Arno, 1936- (Box 87)
  - Hidden variables and the implicate order, [1985]; Bohm, David, 1917-1992 (Box 87)
  - Delayed-choice experiment understood through the quantum potential approach, 1984; Bohm, David, 1917-1992; Dewdney, C.; Hiley, B. J., (Basil J.) (Box 87)
  - [Collected works. Physics volume. Introduction by Rudolf Peierls], 1980-1982; Bohr, Niels Henrik David, 1885-1962 (Box 87)
    Originally enclosed in Series II: Peierls, Rudolf
  - Dansk Kultur, 1941; Bohr, Niels Henrik David, 1885-1962 (Box 87)
    In Danish. Originally enclosed in Series III: Niels Bohr Materials
  - Unity of knowledge, 1954; Bohr, Niels Henrik David, 1885-1962 (Box 87)
    Originally enclosed in Series III: Niels Bohr Materials
  - Field and charge measurements in quantum theory, [1949]; Bohr, Niels Henrik David, 1885-1962; Rosenfeld, L., (Leon), 1904-1974 (Box 87)
  - On the quantum mechanics of collisions, 1926; Born, Max, 1882-1970 (Box 87)
  - Automated search for transient optical point sources, 1975; Boynton, Paul E.; Kennicutt, R. C.; Tomandl, Daniel Anthony, 1947- (Box 87)
  - On the nonlinear capacitance of edged surfaces, 1984; Braginskii, V. B., (Vladimir Borisovich); Viatchanin, S. P. (Box 87)
  - Optimal quantum measurement in the detectors of gravitational radiation, 1978; Braginskii, V. B., (Vladimir Borisovich); Halili, F. A.; Vorontsov, IU. I., (IUrii Ivanovich) (Box 87)
  - Possible photon-detection method for distinguishing between stars and galaxies composed of matter and antimatter, [1977]; Braithwaite, Wilfred J.; Cramer, John G. (Box 87)
  - Energy and entropy costs of information transfer and computing, Bremermann, Hans (Box 87)
  - Hyperspace of constant mean curvature, 1977; Brill, Dieter R. (Box 87)
  - Linearization stability, 1978; Brill, Dieter R. (Box 87)
  - K-surfaces in the Schwarzschild space-time and the construction of lattice cosmologies, [1980]; Brill, Dieter R.; Cavallo, John Michael; Isenberg, James A. (Box 87)
  - New interpretation of the special theory of relativity, 1976; Brisson, David W. (Box 87)
  - Kinetics of cellular cooperative control, 1969; Bronk, Burt V.; Dienes, G. J., (George Julian), b. 1918; Johnson, R. A. (Box 87)
  - Meson physics in Japan (1934-1948), 1978; Brown, Laurie M. (Box 87)
  - [London lecture on Einstein], [1978]; Brown, Salley (Box 87)
    Originally enclosed in Series II: Brown, Salley
  - Derivation of the probability rule, [1981]; Broyles, A. A., (Arthur Augustus), 1923-2009 (Box 87)
  - Chimerical cat; or, Wheeler's dilemma in the interpretation of quantum mechanics, 1979; Brush, Stephen G. (Box 87)
  - Deterministic spacetimes, [1976]; Budic, R., (Robert); Sachs, R. K., (Rainer Kurt), 1932- (Box 87)
  - Scalar time functions: Differentiability, [1976]; Budic, R., (Robert); Sachs, R. K., (Rainer Kurt), 1932- (Box 87)
  - Finiteness and the Type I Superstring, 1986; Burgess, C. P., (Cliff Peter), 1957- (Box 87)
  - Polyakov approach and divergences in open superstrings, 1986; Burgess, C. P., (Cliff Peter), 1957- (Box 87)
  - Open and unoriented strings a la Polyakov, 1986; Burgess, C. P., (Cliff Peter), 1957-; Morris, T. R. (Box 87)
  - Appearance of a rapidly-moving disk, 1983; Burns, Marshall, 1954- (Box 87)
  - On various jointmeasurements of position and momentum observables in quantum theory, 1983; Busch, Paul, 1955-; Lahti, Pekka, (Pekka Johannes), 1948- (Box 87)
  - Large amplitude oscillation of a self-gravitating body, 1961; Bussard, R. W., (Robert W.) (Box 87)
    Originally enclosed Series III: Moon, Origin of the
  - Testimony to the White House Science and Technology Committee Subcommittee on Energy Research and Production, 1982; Bussard, R. W., (Robert W.) (Box 87)
  - Analysis of pp interactions and the quark-parton model, 1973; Bussian, A. E. (Box 87)
  - Subsidiary condition in quantum electrodynamics, 1977; Cahill, Kevin, 1941- (Box 87)
  - Hermitian metric theory and the Weyl-London approach to the "Quantum theory", 1979; Caianiello, Eduardo R., 1921-1993 (Box 87)
  - Quantum geometry and quantum force: Wave and geodesic equations, 1983; Caianiello, Eduardo R., 1921-1993; Marmo, Giuseppe; Scarpetta, G., (Gaetano) (Box 87)
  - Lunar crater Giordano Bruno: AD 1178 impact observations are consistent with modern dynamical observations, 1977; Calame, O., (Odile), 1941-; Mulholland, J. Derral, (John Derral), 1934- (Box 87)
    Originally enclosed in Series II: Smith, Harlan J.
  - Unified theory of strong and gravitational interactions, 1978; Caldirola, Piero, 1914-1984; Pavsic, Matej; Recami, Erasmo (Box 87)
  - Laplacian on asymptotically flat manifolds and the specification of scalar curvature, 1980; Cantor, Murray and Dieter Brill (Box 87)
  - Scientific humanism and the role of the university, 1968; Cantore, Enrico (Box 87)
  - Modern physics and eastern philosophy, 1973; Capra, Fritjof (Box 87)
  - Some investigations into existing states of affairs, 1970; Carpenter, Robert E., (Robert Edmund) (Box 88)
  - [Untitled manuscript], [1970]; Carpenter, Robert E., (Robert Edmund) (Box 88)
  - Contribution of accreting black holes to the background radiation density, 1979; Carr, B. J., (Bernard J.) (Box 88)
  - Anthropic principle and the structure of the physical world, 1979; Carr, B. J., (Bernard J.); Rees, Martin J., 1942- (Box 88)
  - Contribution to the electromagnetic theory, 1981; Carstoiu, John (Box 88)
  - Electromagnetisme, 1984; Carstoiu, John (Box 88)
  - Gravitation: Anisotropie du champ gravifique et ondes ellipsoidales de la gravite, [1970]; Carstoiu, John (Box 88)
  - Gravitation: Propagation d'ondes gravitationnelles et mouvement des planetes. Deviation des rayons lumneux au voisinage du soleil, 1979; Carstoiu, John (Box 88)
  - Magnetohydrodynamic waves, electrohydrodynamic waves, and photons, [1983]; Carstoiu, John (Box 88)
  - Charge and particle conservation in black hole decay, 1974; Carter, B., (Brandon) (Box 88)
  - Retarded Van der Walls forces, 1956; Casimir, H. B. G., (Hendrik Brugt Gerhard), 1909-2000 (Box 88)
  - Space-time free quantum theory, 1981-1982; 2.0 folders; Castellanos, Dario (Box 88)
  - Catastrophe theory and the problem of stellar collapse, 1974; Casti, J. L., (John L.) (Box 88)
  - New simple method to solve transport phenomena for electrons in gases in stationary cases, [1969]; Cavalleri, G., (Giancarlo), 1932- (Box 88)
  - Revision of the relativistic dynamics with variable rest mass and application to relativistic thermodynamics, 1969; Cavalleri, G., (Giancarlo), 1932-; Salgarelli, G. (Box 88)
  - Aksiomatika Einstein-Wheeler-Ove Teorije Superprostora, 1971; 1.0 Volume(s); Cetkovic, Dragoljub (Volume 91)
    In Serbo-Croatian
  - Geometry of twistor theory. I, 1980; Cetkovic, Dragoljub (Box 88)
  - On the cohomology theory of De Rham, [1973]; Cetkovic, Dragoljub (Box 88)
  - Rot[ational] cosmology, 1973; Cetkovic, Dragoljub (Box 88)
  - Selections in topology, 1970; Cetkovic, Dragoljub (Box 88)
  - Twistor theory, 1982; Cetkovic, Dragoljub (Box 88)
  - Twistor theory: An approach to quantum gravity, 1981; Cetkovic, Dragoljub; Penrose, Roger (Box 88)
  - Rest mass quantization in elastic-band theory and possible existence of hitherto unidentified elementary particles, [1972]; Chacko, Thomas (Box 88)
  - Algorithmic information theory, n.d.; Chaitin, Gregory J. (Box 88)
  - Qualitative study of the complete set of solutions of the differential equation of motion of a test particle in the exterior Schwarzschild gravitational field, 1968; Chan, Fu-Kiong (Box 88)
  - Study on the stability of a dense cluster of many gravitating particles in accordance with the theory of general relativity, 1967; Chan, Fu-Kiong; et al (Box 88)
  - Theory of the inconstancy and poly-dimensionality of time, 1973; Chandler, Elisabeth Gordon (Box 89)
  - Pregalatic stars and the cosmic background radiation, [1984]; Chandler, Susan Meyers (Box 89)
  - Bubble device physics, n.d.; Chang, Hsu (Box 89)
  - Forgotten tradition in electrodynamics, and why it must be revived, 1974; Chappell, John E. (Box 89)
  - Nucleon-nuclear wall interaction in scattering processes, 1955; 1.0 Volume(s); Chase, David M. (Volume 92)
  - Proposed unified field theory, [1971]; Chen, Walter (Box 89)
  - Interference and inertia: A superfluid helium interferometer using an internally porous powder and its inertial interactions, 1981; Chiao, Raymond Y. (Box 89)
  - Superfluid helium interferometer as an antenna for gravitational radiation, [1981]; Chiao, Raymond Y. (Box 89)
  - Proposed detection of the Lense-Thirring field with a superfluid helium interferometer, [1981]; Chiao, Raymond Y. and Jeeva S. Anandan (Box 89)
  - Bose rigidity and gravitational radiation, 1982; Chiao, Raymond Y.; Levinsen, M. T., (Mogens T.); Moulthrop, Andrew Alfred (Box 89)
  - Uncommon men, n.d.; Chimbidis, James (Box 89)
  - Neutrino emission processes and stellar evolution. Supernova II, Chiu, H. Y.; Stabler, R. H. (Box 89)
  - On the nature of reality -- A preliminary report, 1980-1981; Chizmarik, Joseph J. (Box 89)
  - On the structure of pregeometry, 1983; Chizmarik, Joseph J. (Box 89)
  - On the structure of the space of participatory observations, 1979; Chizmarik, Joseph J. (Box 89)
  - Chronos principle, 1974; Christodoulou, Demetrios, 1951- (Box 89)
    -- See also Series I: Christodoulou, Demetrios
  - Investigations in gravitational collapse and the physics of black holes, 1971; Christodoulou, Demetrios, 1951- (Box 89)
  - On quantum geometrodynamics, 1972; Christodoulou, Demetrios, 1951- (Box 89)
  - Reversible and irreversible transformations in black hole physics, 1970; Christodoulou, Demetrios, 1951- (Box 89)
  - Gravitational synchrotron radiation, 1973; 1.0 Volume(s); Chrzanowski, Paul (Volume 93)
    - See also Series VI: Misner, Charles W. "Gravitational synchrotron radiation"
  - Nonlinear functional analysis and numerical computations of the strong interaction S-matrix; Applications to pion-pion dispersion relations, 1970; Chung, Kuk Pyo (Box 89)
  - Theory and experiments in general relativity and other metric theories of gravity, 1984; Ciufolini, Ignazio, 1951- (Box 89)
  - Trilocal electron, 1968; Clapp, Roger E. (Box 89)
  - Theory of α matter, [1965]; Clark, J. W., (John Walter), 1935-; Wang, Tso-Pin (Box 89)
  - Case against pre-acceleration, [1979]; Cohn, Jack, 1932- (Box 89)
  - Shear-free perfect fluids with zero magnetic Weyl tensor, 1983; Collins, Christopher B. (Box 89)
  - Class of shear-free perfect fluids in general relativity I, 1983; Collins, Christopher B.; White, A. J. (Box 89)
  - Class of shear-free perfect fluids in general relativity II, 1983; Collins, Christopher B.; White, A. J. (Box 89)
  - Mathematical basis of physical laws, 1980; Collins, R. Eugene (Box 89)
  - On non-electromagnetic interactions in quantum mechanics; A theory of elementary particles, 1980; Collins, R. Eugene (Box 89)
  - Commemoration of the Fiftieth Anniversary of Niels Bohr's First Papers on Atomic Constitution, 1963; 4.0 folders (Box 90)
  - Princeton's John Archibald Wheeler: "True Searcher" of the universe, 1975; Conniff, James C. G. (Box 90)
  - Helicite et impulsion transversale d'un fermion relativiste extreme dans un accelerateur circulaire, [1964]; Costa de Beauregard, O., (Olivier) (Box 90)
  - Relationship between man and his environment -- A mathematical model, [1973]; Costagliola, Francesco (Box 90)
  - Neutrinos from electron-positron pair annihilation in supernovae, 1980; Courvoisier, Thierry J. - L., 1953- (Box 90)
  - Generalized absorber theory and the Einstein-Podolsky-Rosen paradox, [1980]; Cramer, John G. (Box 90)
  - Transactional interpretation of quantum mechanics, 1983; Cramer, John G. (Box 90)
  - Physicist as consultant-entrepeneur, [1977]; Cranberg, Lawrence (Box 90)
  - Scientist's obligation to help prevent nuclear war, [1983]; Cranberg, Lawrence (Box 90)
  - [Proposal], [1977]; Crawford, John David (Box 90)
  - Chaos in discrete systems, [1981]; Crutchfield, James P., (James Patrick); Packard, N. H.; Shaw, R. S. (Box 90)
  - "Classical-radius" and gravitational field of a charged particle, [1974]; Dadhich, N., (Naresh) (Box 90)
  - On mass (gravitational and inertial) of a charged particle, [1974]; Dadhich, N., (Naresh) (Box 90)
  - Quantum mechanics and the structure and dynamics of linguistic systems: A model for cognition, 1985; Damiris, Nicholas (Box 90)
  - Comments on fixed poles in photoproduction amplitudes, 1969; Dashen, Roger F.; Lee, S. Y., (Shyh-Yuan) (Box 90)
  - Time variation of the coupling constants, [1972]; Davies, P. C. W. (Box 90)
    Page proofs. Originally enclosed in Series II: British Association for the Advancement of Science
  - American physicists and the Copenhagen experience, 1920-1940, 1984; Davies, Shannon Melinda (Box 90)
  - Academic renegade, 1980; Davis, Derek S. B. (Box 90)
  - Gauge transformations in the linearized quantum theory of gravity, n.d.; Davis, Lincoln R. (Box 90)
  - Vector and tensor synchrotron radiation in a Schwarzschild metric, Davis, Lincoln R. (Box 90)
  - Instead of Alfven waves, [1978]; De, Bibhas Ranjan, 1946- (Box 90)
  - Revision of magnetohydrodynamics, [1978]; De, Bibhas Ranjan, 1946- (Box 90)
  - Atmospheric window and anthropic principle, 1980; Dean, William Edwin (Box 90)
  - Effect of gravitational radiation reaction on a three body system, 1984; Dean, William Edwin (Box 90)
  - Is radioactive decay really exponential?, 1980; Dean, William Edwin (Box 90)
  - Preliminary results for gravitational radiation from self-gravitating disk fragments, 1983; Dean, William Edwin (Box 90)
    Originally enclosed in Series II: Dean, William
  - Closed-loop postulate; A brief summary, 1986; DeGracia, Donald J. (Box 90)
  - Holistic philosophy with implications for physics, 1987; DeGracia, Donald J. (Box 90)
  - Message passing semantics for conceptual modeling, 1982; De Jong, Peter; Hewitt, Carl (Box 90)
  - Aristotle-totle-totle, 1971; Delbrück, Max (Box 90)
  - On Wheeler's "Rule of Unanimity" in quantum cosmology, 1979; Demaret, Jacques (Box 90)
  - Hamiltonian formalism for perfect fluids in general relativity, [1979]; Demaret, Jacques; Moncrief, Vincent (Box 90)
  - Operators and states in the "Field representation" and vacuum fluctuations, [1956]; Dempster, Hugh (Box 91)
  - Pointwise field representation: Operators and states in functional form, [1957]; Dempster, Hugh (Box 91)
  - OD effect: A new physical phenomena, 1973; DePalma, Bruce E. (Box 91)
  - Theory of relativity, Part II, uniform connectivity, 1973; DePalma, Bruce E. (Box 91)
  - What is buckling?, 1962; Dessauer, Gerhard (Box 91)
  - Boundary effects in quantum field theory, 1978; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
    Ph.D. thesis
  - Consciousness and the observer in quantum theory, 1977; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - Is there a fundamental bound on the rate at which information can be processed, [1981]; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - On concious physical systems, 1977; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - On power, [1978]; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - On Wheeler's notion of "Law without law" in physics, 1983-1985; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - Quantum theory as a universal physical theory, 1981-[1982]; 2.0 folders; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - Quantum theory, the Church-Turing hypothesis, and universal quantum computers, 1983-1985; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - Three connections between Everett's interpretation and experiment, 1984; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - Uncertainty in quantum measurements, 1982; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - [Untitled], 1980; Deutsch, David, 1953- (Box 91)
  - Negative energy radiation and the second law of thermodynamics, 1982; Deutsch, David, 1953-; Ottewill, Adrian; Sciama, D. W. (Dennis William), 1926- (Box 91)
  - Five crucial tests of the cosmic distance scale using the galaxy as a fundamental standard, 1982; De Vaucouleurs, Gerard, 1918-1995 (Box 91)
  - Probable compact companion to PSR 1913+16, n.d.; Devinney, Edward J. (Box 91)
  - PSR 1913+16 and two effects of general relativity, Devinney, Edward J.; Gilmore, Robert, 1941- (Box 91)
  - Quantum gravity: The new synthesis, [1977]; DeWitt, Bryce S., (Bryce Seligman), 1923- (Box 91)
  - Superconductors and gravitational drag, 1966; DeWitt, Bryce S., (Bryce Seligman), 1923- (Box 91)
  - Radiation damping in a gravitational field, 1959; DeWitt, Bryce S., (Bryce Seligman), 1923- and Robert W. Brehme (Box 91)
    Originally enclosed in Series III: Gravitational Radiation
  - Path integration quantization, [1982]; DeWitt-Morette, Cécile (Box 91)
  - Caustic problem in quantum mechanics with application to scattering theory, [1982]; DeWitt-Morette, Cécile; Nelson, B. D., (Bruce D.); Zhang, Tianrong (Box 91)
  - Feynman-Kac formula in phase space with application to coherent state transitions, [1982]; DeWitt-Morette, Cécile; Zhang, Tianrong (Box 91)
  - Path integrals and conservation laws, [1982]; DeWitt-Morette, Cécile; Zhang, Tianrong (Box 91)
  - Constraint algebra in eleven dimensional supergravity, 1984; Diaz Montoya, Alvaro H. (Box 92)
  - Hamiltonian formulation of supergravity in eleven dimensions, [1984]-1985; Diaz Montoya, Alvaro H. (Box 92)
  - [Untitled], 1984; Diaz Montoya, Alvaro H. (Box 92)
  - Early Work: Logical development of quantum physics and the Raman effect in the atom; Coherence brightened laser, 1939, n.d.; 1.0 Volume(s); Dicke, Robert H., (Robert Henry) (Volume 94)
    Spine reads "Early work"
  - Observational foundation of Einstein's theory of gravitation, the gravitational acceleration, 1981; Dicke, Robert H., (Robert Henry) (Box 92)
    Page proofs. Originally enclosed in Series III: Albert Einstein Material
  - On observing the absence of an atom, 1985; Dicke, Robert H., (Robert Henry) (Box 92)
  - Differential rotation and the solar oblateness, 1967; Dicke, Robert H., (Robert Henry); Goldenberg, H. Mark (Box 92)
  - Relativistic wave equation with only positive energy solutions, [1971]; Dirac, P. A. M., (Paul Adrien Maurice), 1902-1984 (Box 92)
    Address. Originally enclosed in Series I: Wigner, Eugene P. 17 May 1971
  - Chemical geometrodynamics, [1977]; Dougherty, Ralph (Box 92)
  - Chemical geometrodynamics, [1978]; Dougherty, Ralph; et al (Box 92)
  - Effects of electric and magnetic fields on prochiral chemical reactions: Macroscopic electric and magnetic fields can cause asymmetric synthesis, [1977]; Dougherty, Ralph; Rhodes, William T. (Box 92)
  - Guidance-Basic principles, 1964; Draper, C. S., (Charles Stark); Wrigley, Walter (Box 92)
    Originally enclosed in Series III: Measurement of Space and Time
  - Infrared topology on a massless Boson Fock space, [1978]; Dubisch, Russell (Box 92)
  - Supergravity, the seven-sphere, and spontaneous symmetry breaking, 1982; Duff, Michael J., 1949- (Box 92)
  - Superunification and the seven-sphere, [1983]; Duff, Michael J., 1949- (Box 92)
  - Compactification of d=11 supergravity on K3 x T 3, 1983; Duff, Michael J., 1949-; Nilsson, Bengt E. W.; Pope, Christopher N. (Box 92)
  - Spontaneous supersymmetry breaking by the squashed seven-sphere, 1983; Duff, Michael J., 1949-; Nilsson, Bengt E. W.; Pope, Christopher N. (Box 92)
  - Cosmological constant in spontaneously compactified d=11 supergravity, 1982; Duff, Michael J., 1949-; Orzalesi, C. A. (Box 92)
  - Kaluza-Klein supergravity and the seven sphere space, 1983; Duff, Michael J., 1949-; Pope, Christopher N. (Box 92)
  - Spontaneous compactification of supergravity on the three-sphere, 1982; Duff, Michael J., 1949-; Townsend, P. K.; Van Nieuwenhuizen, Peter (Box 92)
  - Range of time delays for the double quasar 0957+561A,B, 1980; Dyer, C. C., (Charles Chester), 1946-; Roeder, Robert Charles, 1937- (Box 92)
  - Numerical simulation of axially symmetric gravitational collapse, 1980; 2.0 folders; Dykema, Pieter Geer (Box 92)
  - Fundamental constants and their time variations, 1971; Dyson, Freeman J. (Box 92)
  - Roots: Option for the Phi Beta Kappa literary exercies at Harvard University, June 3, 1986, Dyson, Freeman J. (Box 92)